Guys, I'm not from Venezuela. I'm from
Iran. We have um almost the same
situation in Iran. We have a dictator
and a dictatorship government that uh
they've been murdering our people for 70
for 47 years and we are waiting for that
day to have freedom back. And
we don't want Islam anymore cuz Islam
destroyed our country and Islamic
government destroyed
everything about us.
I just wanted to explain uh that we feel
the people in Venezuela cuz we we are
living that situation. We are living uh
the experience of having a dictator,
having somebody that have control and
power over all the people and they
decide for 80 million people in Iran how
to live. And [clears throat] they are
giving us the worst nightmare for 47
years.
And
they've been executing. They've been um
they've they've been um controlling
women. [clears throat] They've they've
they've done a lot of evil things in
Iran that it needs to stop. We are over
it. Like um this is not the first time
that our people are protesting. And the
same thing happened in Venezuela cuz we
don't have power. We don't have weapons
to defend and take over the like
overthrow the country and the
government.
And the only way that we are hoping
something happens is the same thing
happened to Venezuela cuz we need
someone like Trump to help us. Believe
it or not, we want that. The time that
Israel and United States attack Iran, we
were cheering. You were happy
cuz you guys never understand how it
feels
to
live like a hole in Iran, like a
dog. Even animals don't have good life
in Iran.
Inflation is that high that a dollar
worth
times more than our money 140 times a
dollar
because of the sanction because the
Islamic Republic is a terrorism or
terrorist Islamic organization
and United States
and other countries They don't want to
to deal with them.
They made us to look like a terrorist.
They see us Iranian a terrorist person
which we are not.
And
it's just it's really bad like um if I
want to explain everything about this
government and all the things that they
have done, I I can I can write a book.
The experience that we have after the
Islamic revolution,
it's it's crazy
the things that we have seen and we are
living
right now.
Yeah. We just want it to be over just
like uh to be honest, I'm jealous of the
people in Venezuela.
They're so happy. I feel them. They have
the right to be happy.
Yeah.